Mitzi Prease Goolsby

11 Parkins Grove Ct. Greenville, South Carolina 29607 Phone: (864) 299-4706 Email: mitzipgoolsby@aol.com

CAREER PROFILE:

Over ten years experience as a Support Specialist. A hardworking, dependable young woman willing to learn and accept responsibilities. A highly motivated individual with exceptional time management, and organizational skills. Proficient in Windows for Word, Outlook, PowerPoint and Excel. Excellent verbal and written communication skills.

EDUCATION

2002 Certificate in Medical Transcription, Greenville Medical & Business
Training Center
1990-1994 Bachelor of Science in Business Administration with a
Concentration in Management, South Carolina State University

1986-1990 Diploma, Southside High School

EMPLOYMENT

2003-2015 Senior Telecom Analyst, AccessPoint Inc.

Responsible for providing support to Dealer Managers and Agents with competitive cost analysis proposals, rate information, and available services offered for new customers. Assist dealer/agents with completion of paperwork and with partner support site. Pull existing customers reports to re-term accounts and complete individual case basis analysis to offer better rates to keep business. *Recognized by co-workers as the Most Valuable Player on the team for my hard work and dedication.

2001-2002 Systems Entry Specialist, NewSouth Communications

Responsible for establishing new customer accounts accurately in

billing system and reviewing orders after implementation.

2000-2001 Customer Relations Manager, Qwest Communications

Responsible for management of customer base, worked with customers to upgrade services, provide information, handle problems and positively impact revenue flow. Gathered information and provided customized monthly reports to the customer base. Tracked and ensured timely implementation of

new services.

1998-2000 Distributor Support Representative, Qwest Communications

Provided support to Distributors in order processing. Screened and processed incoming distributor orders. Provided sales/promotion

information and instruction on order procedures. Monitored orders to ensure they achieve turn-up in an acceptable time frame.

*Recognized by Distributors for my professionalism and my ability for following orders through to ensure projected revenue.

1995-1998

Customer Service Representative, Qwest Communications Researched and effectively presented solutions to inquiries from existing business customers. Informed customers on dialing procedures, rates, and other telecommunication services. Processed new/changed orders for customers in a timely manner. *Recognized by management with HERO AWARD for maximum utilization of available resources and for providing efficient services.

1994-1995

Sales Associates, Rich's Department Store
Provided the highest quality of customer service by displaying appropriate selling skills and using product information.

Maintained professional image by approaching customers with a smile and a positive attitude. Handled customers' problems and complaints with good judgment.

* Received numerous compliments from peers and customers on my courteous and professional service.

REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST